shopback.com 2015-05-19

# Privacy & Security | FAQ - ShopBack.com

Privacy and Security

What is ShopBack’s privacy policy?  
How secure is my credit card information?  
Will ShopBack sell my information or my past transactions?  
Why must “cookies” be enabled to qualify for cashback?  
Personal Data Protection Policy – Singapore  
Privacy Policy – Malaysia  
Personal Data Notice – Malaysia  
Citibank Terms and Conditions (Singapore)  
Citibank Globeshopper Terms & Conditions (Singapore)

* * *

### What is ShopBack’s privacy policy?

At ShopBack, we believe in respecting and protecting our members’ personal data. View our Personal Data Protection Policy for Singapore [here](http://www.shopback.com/help/privacysecurity#pdpa).

* * *

### How secure is my credit card information?

ShopBack aims to partner only with stores providing high levels of credit card processing security. We do not process or capture your credit card information.

* * *

### Will ShopBack sell my information or my past transactions?

Absolutely not. For more details, please view our Personal Data Protection Policy [here](http://www.shopback.com/help/privacysecurity#pdpa).

* * *

### Why must “cookies” be enabled to qualify for cashback?

Cookies allow us to track your transactions with our Merchant Partners. This allows us to credit cashback rewards to your ShopBack account.

* * *

### Personal Data Protection Policy – Singapore

ShopBack collects information to understand your needs better. This helps us to improve our services and the way we communicate with you. We know that privacy is important to you and we strive to be as open and transparent as possible in how we serve you.The purpose of this document is to inform you how ShopBack manages, collects, uses and discloses your Personal Data. In Singapore, such business activities are subjected to the Personal Data Protection Act (No. 26 of 2012) (“The Act”). We conduct our business in compliance with The Act and have implemented additional measures to protect your personal information. ShopBack’s Personal Data Protection Policy aims to help you understand how we collect, use, share and protect your personal information ShopBack may update this Personal Data Protection Policy to ensure that it is consistent with industry trends and/or any changes in legal or regulatory requirements. Subject to your rights at law, you agree to be bound by the prevailing terms of the Personal Data Protection Policy as updated from time to time on our website.

**Personal Data**

In this Personal Data Protection Policy, “Personal Data” refers to any data, whether true or not, about an individual who can be identified from that data or from that data and other information to which we have or are likely to have access, including data in our records as may be updated from time to time. Examples of such Personal Data you may provide to us include your name, NRIC, passport or other identification number, telephone numbers, mailing address, email address, network data and any other information relating to any individuals which you have provided us in any forms you may have submitted to us, or via other forms of interaction with you.

**Collection of Personal Data**

ShopBack does not sell, share or trade customers’ personal data collected online with third parties.

**Ways we collect your Personal Information**

ShopBack collects Personal Data either directly from you or from your authorised representatives (i.e. persons whom you have authorised, persons who have been validly identified as being you or your authorised representative pursuant to our security procedures), from third parties, or from publicly available sources or through our websites.

We collect your Personal Data when you:

  * Register for our services and/or submit any forms relating to any of our Products and Services
  * Use some of our services, for example, websites and apps including establishing any online accounts with us
  * Sign up for alerts or newsletters
  * Contact us with enquiries or request for assistance
  * Participate in a competition, lucky draw or survey
  * Visit our website
  * Are referenced by business partners and/or third parties
  * Submit your Personal Data to us for any other reasons When you browse our website, you generally do so anonymously but please see below for information regarding the use of cookies.

When you provide us with any Personal Data to a third party (e.g. information of your spouse, children, parents, and/or employees), by submitting such information to us, you represent to us that you have obtained the consent of the third party to provide us with their Personal Data for the respective purposes. You should ensure that all Personal Data submitted to us is complete , accurate, true and correct. Failure on your part to do so may result in our inability to provide you with the Products and Services that you have requested.

**The information we collect**

When you create a ShopBack account, the personal information we collect may include your:

  * Identity: This includes your e-mail address, date of birth, gender as well as payment-related information such as PayPal account details, device ID and IP address.
  * Interactions with us: Recordings of your phone call with us, an email you sent or other records of any contact you have with us.
  * Account information: Details relating to your ShopBack account.
  * Information on your use of our services: Use of cookies to track interaction with the website including clicks and redirects.
  * Preferences: This is based on what you have shared with us on how you would like to be contacted, and your preferred products and brands for example.
  * Information from other organizations: These organizations include fraud-prevention agencies, affiliate stores or individuals we believe you have authorized to provide your personal details on your behalf.

**Use of Personal Information**

We may use your information for:

  * Service Administration
  * Process your orders and activate or deactivate services
  * Enable us to process payments
  * Respond to enquiries and requests from you or people you have authorised
  * Matching any Personal Data held which relates to you for any of the purposes listed herein
  * Inform you about service updates
  * Provide directory assistance
  * Conduct market research and customer satisfaction surveys to improve our services; develop new products and personalize the services we offer you
  * Perform market analysis
  * Provide updates, offers and deliver relevant advertising, including periodic newsletters with your prior consent or if otherwise permitted under local laws and regulations
  * Inform you of service and security issues
  * Prevent and detect fraud or other crimes
  * Conduct internal audits
  * Ensure the safety and security of our properties and systems
  * Conduct checks against money laundering, terrorism financing and related risks
  * Meet legal, regulatory and other requirements including providing assistance to law enforcements, judicial and other government agencies
  * Meeting or complying with any applicable rules, laws, regulations, codes of practice or guidelines issued by any legal or regulatory bodies which are binding on ShopBack (including but not limited to responding to regulatory complaints, disclosing to regulatory bodies and conducting audit checks, due diligence and investigations).
  * Service Enhancements
  * Promotion of benefits
  * Offer rewards and promotions, and share promotional benefits and loyalty programmes that you qualify for
  * Provide updates, offers and deliver relevant advertising, including periodic newsletters with your prior consent or if otherwise permitted under local laws and regulations
  * Security and risk management
  * Inform you of service and security issues
  * Additional Purposes Where permitted under the Act, ShopBack may also collect, use and disclose your Personal Data for the following “Additional Purposes”
  * Analytics and tracking
  * Providing additional Products and Services benefits to you, including promotions, loyalty and reward programmes from ShopBack
  * Matching Personal Data with other data collected for other purposes and from other sources (including third parties) in connection with the provision, marketing or offering of Products and Services by ShopBack
  * Leaders generation and management for marketing ShopBack’s Products and Services • Administering contests, competitions and marketing campaigns, and personalising your experience at ShopBack’s touch points
  * Communicating to you advertisements involving details of our Products and Services, special offers and rewards, either to our customers generally, or which we have identified may be of interest to you (including but not limited to upselling, cross selling and online marketing)
  * Organising promotional events and corporate social responsibility projects
  * Purposes which are reasonably related to the aforesaid In addition, where permitted under the Act and subject to the provisions of any applicable law, your Personal Data may be disclosed, for ShopBack Additional Purposes, to the vendors or other third party service providers in connection with promotion and services offered by ShopBack.

ShopBack may also collect, use and disclose your Personal Data for the following “Preferred Partners Additional Purposes”

  * Conducting market research and surveys to enable us to understand and determine customer location, preferences and demographics to develop special offers and marketing programmes with our preferred partners
  * Matching Personal Data with other data collected for other purposes and from other sources (including third parties) in connection with the provision, marketing or offering of Products and Services (including promotions, loyalty and reward programmes) by our preferred partners
  * Leads generation and management for marketing the products and services offered by our preferred partners
  * Administering contests, competitions and marketing campaigns in connection with the products and services offered by our preferred partners
  * Communicating to you advertisements involving details of the products, services, special offers and rewards offered by our preferred partners, either to our customers generally, (including but not limited to upselling, cross selling and online marketing)
  * Purposes which are reasonably related to the aforesaid In addition, where permitted under the Act and subject to the provisions of any applicable law, your Personal Data may be disclosed, for Preferred Partners’ Additional Purposes, to the vendors or other third party service providers in connection with promotions and services offered by ShopBack’s preferred partners.

We will not use your personal data for purposes other than what we have informed you, or which are permitted under local law and regulations. We will not offer, publish or share your personal data with third parties outside of ShopBack for commercial purposes, without seeking your explicit permission. We will retain your information for only as long as there is a business or legal need. Further, we will use the information you provide to administer your account with us; verify and carry out financial transactions in relation to payments you make online; audit the downloading of data from our website; improve the layout and/or content of the pages of our website and customize them for users; identify visitors on our website; carry out research on our users’ demographics; send you information we think you may find useful or which you have requested from us, including information about our products and services, provided you have indicated that you have not objected to being contacted for these purposes When you register as a user on ShopBack, we will also use your personal information to send you marketing and/or promotional materials from time to time. You can unsubscribe from marketing information at any time through My Subscriptions on the account page or using the unsubscribe function within the electronic marketing material.

**Updating your Personal Information**

You can update your personal information any time by accessing your account on ShopBack website. ShopBack is receptive to requests from individuals for information relating to their Personal Data that is in our possession or control. We are also receptive to queries from individuals about the way their personal information has been used in the past year by us or by third parties to whom we have disclose the Personal Data. We will correct any error in your Personal Data upon request.

**Security of your Personal Information**

ShopBack ensures that all information collected will be safely and securely stored.

We protect your personal information by:

  * Restricting access to personal information
  * Maintaining technology products to prevent unauthorized computer access
  * Securely destroying your personal information when it’s no longer needed for our record retention purposes.

**Disclosure of Personal Information**

We will not share your information with any other organizations other than related companies and those third parties directly related to the delivery of the products you have purchased from ShopBack website. In exceptional circumstances, ShopBack may be required to disclose personal information, such as when there are grounds to believe that disclosure is necessary to prevent a threat to life or health, or for law enforcement purposes. ShopBack is committed to complying with the Personal Data Protection Act 2012. ShopBack will take reasonable steps to protect your Personal Data against unauthorised disclosure. Subjected to the provisions of any applicable law, your Personal Data may be disclosed, for the purposes listed above (where applicable), to the following:

  * ShopBack’s related corporations and employees to provide content, Products and Services to you, address your questions and requests in relation to your customer accounts, subscription and billing or order arrangements with us as well as Products and Services, to activate, deactivate, install, maintain and operate our systems and/or services
  * Companies providing services relating to insurance and consultancy to ShopBack
  * Agents, contractors or third party service providers who provide operational services to ShopBack, such as telecommunications, information technology, payment, printing, billing, payroll, processing, technical services, training, market research, call centre or other services to ShopBack
  * Vendors or third party service providers in connection with marketing promotions and services offered by ShopBack or its preferred partners
  * Commercial shops and retailers in relation to providing rewards and benefits
  * Any business partner, investor, assignee or transferee (actual or prospective) to facilitate business asset transactions (which may extent to any merger, acquisition or asset sale) involving any of the Companies
  * Our professional advisers such as auditors and lawyers
  * Relevant government regulators, statutory boards or authorities or law enforcement agencies to comply with any laws, rules, guidelines and regulations or schemes imposed by any governmental authority
  * Any other party to whom you authorise us to disclose your Personal Data to

**Sharing your information**

We may share your information with:

  * Business partners and affiliate stores we work with to deliver services you have subscribed to
  * Industry regulators and other government organizations, as required by local laws and regulations
  * Electronic payment vendors for purposes such as facilitating cash back payments
  * Research institutions for market analysis purposes

Your information is disclosed to the above only for relevant purposes (please refer to those mentioned in this Policy) or to protect the interests of our customers. In some cases, we encrypt, anonymize and aggregate the information before sharing it. Anonymizing means stripping the information of personally identifiable features. Aggregating means presenting the information in groups or segments eg. age groups. We will also ensure that overseas organisations we work with observe strict confidentiality and data protection obligations.

**Protecting your information**

We have implemented stringent measures to secure and protect your information. These include:

  * Safeguards to prevent security breaches in our network and database systems
  * Limits on access to information in our systems and the systems of our business partners and affiliate stores
  * Strict verification processes to prevent unauthorized access to information

**Collection of Computer Data**

When you visit ShopBack, our company servers will automatically record information that your browser ends whenever you visit a website. This data may include:

  * Your company’s IP address
  * Browser type
  * Webpage you were visiting before you came to our site
  * The pages within ShopBack you visit
  * The time spent on those pages, items and information searched on our site, access times and dates, and other statistics.

This information is collected for analysis and evaluation in order to help us improve our site and the services and products we provide. This data will not be used in association with any other personal information.

**Use of cookies**

ShopBack uses “cookies”, where a small data file is sent to your browser to store and track information about you when you enter our website. The cookie is used to track information such as the number of users and their frequency of use, profiles of users and their preferred sites. Core information collected on our website includes:

  * The number of page views (or page impressions) that occur on ShopBack website
  * The number of unique visitors to the ShopBack website
  * How long these unique visitors spent on the website when they visit
  * Common entry and exit points into ShopBack website
  * Affiliate store links that each member clicks

Most internet browsers provide you the option to turn off the processing of cookies but this may result in the loss of functionality, restrict your use of the website and/or delay or affect the way in which it operates. Advertisements on the ShopBack website may be provided by third party advertisers and their agencies. These may generate cookies to track how many people have seen a particular advertisement (or use the services of third parties to do this), and to track how many people have seen it more than once. ShopBack does not control these third parties and their cookie policies and if you have questions about their cookie policies, please contact ShopBack and we will try our best to assist by providing you information about these third party advertising agencies. ShopBack is not responsible for the Personal Data policies (including Personal Data Protection and cookies), content or security of any third party websites linked to ShopBack.

**Google Analytics**

ShopBack uses features of Google Analytics. Please see this link <http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners> for how your data is collected and <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout> for how to opt out of any Google Analytics tracking. As part of the above, ShopBack may use Google Analytics features based on Display Advertising, including but not restricted to the following: Remarking, Google Display Network Impression Reporting, DoubleClick Campaign manager Integration, and Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting. Using the Google Ads Settings (<https://www.google.com/settings/ads>), you can opt out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize Google Display Network ads. ShopBack also uses Remarketing with Google Analytics to advertise online; third party vendors, including Google, may show ShopBack ads across the Internet. ShopBack and third party vendors, including Google, use first party cookies (such as Google Analytics cookie) and third party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) together to inform, optimize, and serve ads based on the visitors’ past visit to ShopBack, as well as report how ad impressions, other use of ads services, and interactions with these ad impressions and ad services are related to visits to ShopBack. When you log into ShopBack website, ShopBack with the help of Google Analytics may use your browsing behaviour to connect it with any other data that has previously been provided by you, in accordance with this Personal Data Protection Policy.

**Respecting your consent**

Our marketing newsletters aim to update you about our exclusive offers, rewards programme, and special deals from our preferred partners. Should you wish to withdraw your consent for us to send you sales, marketing or promotional information via marketing newsletters, you can do so by clicking the “unsubscribe” link at the bottom of each newsletter.

**Changes to the Personal Data Protection Policy**

ShopBack reserves the right to modify and update the Personal Data Protection Policy at any time to ensure that it is consistent with industry trends and/or any changes in legal or regulatory requirements. Subject to your rights at law, you agree to be bound by the prevailing terms of the Personal Data Protection Policy as updated from time to time on our website. Any changes to this policy will be published on our site.

**Contacting Us**

For any questions relating to your Personal Data or about our Personal Data Protection Policy, you may contact our Data Privacy Officer at customer@shopback.com.

**Governing Law**

This Personal Data Protection Policy and your use of this website shall be governed in all respects by the laws of Singapore.

* * *

### Privacy Policy – Malaysia

This Privacy Policy discloses the privacy practices for the ShopBack Malaysia website (the “Website”). ShopBack is committed to protecting your privacy online in compliance with Personal Data Protection Act 2010 (“the Act”). Please read the following to learn what information we collect from you (the “User” or the “End User”) and how we use that information. If you have any questions about our privacy policy, please contact our Data Privacy Officer at customer@shopback.com. By accessing or using our website, you expressly consent to us for our processing of your personal data, you acknowledge that you have read, understand and agree to be bound to all the terms of this privacy policy and our website terms of use, and we are in full compliance with the Act. If you do not agree to these terms, kindly exit this page and refrain from accessing or using the website.

**Changes to Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make substantial (to which degree is at the sole discretion of the ShopBack team) changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of notice on our home page.

**Types of Information Collected and Uses of Collected Information**

We collect two types of information about our Website Users: Personally Identifiable Information and Non-Personally Identifiable Information.

Personally Identifiable Information: Personally Identifiable Information is information that pertains to a specific End User. When you engage in certain activities on the Website, such as creating an account, ordering a product or service from us or our partners, submitting content and/or posting content in discussion forums, entering a contest or sweepstakes sponsored by us or our partners, filling out a survey, posting a review, sending us or our partners feedback, requesting information about our services, submitting an affiliate agreement, applying for a job, posting a video or signing up for special offers from third parties through the Website (collectively, “Identification Activities”), we may ask you to provide certain information about yourself. It is optional for you to engage in an Identification Activity. If you elect to engage in an Identification Activity, however, we may ask you to provide us with certain personal information about yourself, such as your first and last name, mailing address (including zip code), email address, telephone number and date of birth. Depending on the activity, some of the information we ask you to provide is identified as mandatory and some is identified as voluntary. If you do not provide the mandatory information for a particular activity that requires it, you will not be permitted to engage in that activity.

Non-Personally Identifiable Information: Non-Personally Identifiable Information is information that does not identify a specific End User. This type of information may include things like the Uniform Resource Locator (“URL”) of the website you visited before coming to our Website, the URL of the website you visit after leaving our Website, the type of browser you are using and your Internet Protocol (“IP”) address. We, and/or our authorized Third Party Service Providers and Advertisers, may automatically collect this information when you visit our Website through the use of electronic tools like Cookies and Web beacons or Pixel tags, as described in the “Release of Non-Personally Identifiable Information” section and “Data Tracking” section of this Privacy Policy. We use Non-Personally Identifiable Information to troubleshoot, administer the Website, analyze trends, gather demographic information, comply with applicable law, and cooperate with law enforcement activities. We may also share this information with our authorized Third Party Service Providers and Advertisers to measure the overall effectiveness of our online advertising, content, and programming.

**Release of Personally Identifiable Information**

We will not share, sell, rent, or trade your Personally Identifiable Information with other parties except as provided below: We may share your information with Authorized Third Party Service Providers. We provide services and products through third parties. These “Third Party Service Providers” perform functions on our behalf, like sending out and distributing our administrative and promotional emails or text messages. We may share your Personally Identifiable Information with such Service Providers to fulfill orders, deliver packages, send postal or email, administer contests or sweepstakes, remove repetitive information on customer lists, analyze data, provide marketing assistance, provide search results and links, process credit card payments, operate the Website, troubleshoot, and provide customer service. We may also collect personal information from individuals and companies (“Affiliates”) with whom we have business relationships and may share your information with Service Providers to accomplish our administrative tasks. However, the use of your Personally Identifiable Information by such parties is governed by the privacy policies of such parties and is not subject to our control. We may remarket your information. Remarketing is a way for us to connect with users, based upon your past interactions with the ShopBack Malaysia website. Third-party marketing vendors may be hired by ShopBack Malaysia to perform remarketing services. As a result, third-party vendors, including Google, may show ShopBack Malaysia ads on sites on the internet. Third-party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user’s prior visits to ShopBack Malaysia’s website. Users may opt out of Google’s use of cookies by visiting the Google advertising opt-out page at http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html. This information is used only for remarketing purposes and will not be used by them for any other purpose. We may share your information in a Business Transfer. As with any other business, we could merge with, or be acquired by another company. If this occurs, the successor company would acquire the information we maintain, including Personally Identifiable Information. However, Personally Identifiable Information would remain subject to this Privacy Policy. We may share your information for our Protection and the Protection of Others. We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Website; enforce or apply this Privacy Policy, our Website Terms of Use or other agreements; or protect the rights, property or safety of the Website, its Users or others.

**Release of Non-Personally Identifiable Information**

We may disclose or share Non-Personally Identifiable Information with Partners and Advertisers. For example, we may share aggregated demographic information (which does not include any Personally Identifiable Information) with “Third Party Advertisers” or “Third Party Advertising Companies” and other parties as provided below: We may use Third Party Advertising Companies to serve ads when you visit our Website. These companies may use Non-Personally Identifiable Information about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide, through the use of network tags, advertisements about goods and services that may be of interest to you. Some of these Third Party Advertising Companies may be advertising networks that are members of the Network Advertising Initiative (“NAI”). If you would like more information about any NAI member company, or you would like to opt-out of targeted advertising from any NAI member company, click here: http://www.networkadvertising.org/consumer/opt_out.asp We also use Third Party Service Providers to track and analyze Non-Personally Identifiable usage and volume statistical information from our Users to administer our Website and constantly improve its quality. We may also publish this information for promotional purposes or as a representative audience for Advertisers. Please note that this is not Personally Identifiable Information, only general summaries of the activities of our Users. Such data is collected on our behalf, and is owned and used by us.

**Updating and Correcting Information**

We believe that you should have the ability to access and edit the Personally Identifiable Information you provide us. You may change any of your Personally Identifiable Information by logging into your account and accessing the “ACCOUNT” section of the site or sending us an email at help@shopback.com. Please indicate your name and email address, and what information you would like to update when you contact us. We encourage you to promptly update your Personally Identifiable Information if it changes. You may ask to have the information on your account deleted or removed; however, because we keep track of past transactions, you cannot delete information associated with past transactions on the Website. In addition, in may be impossible for us to completely delete all of your information because we periodically backup information.

**User Choices on Collection and Use of Information**

As discussed above, you can always choose not to provide information, although it may be required to engage in a certain activity on the Website. As a condition of purchase of our products and services, we will send you Administrative and Promotional emails. We will send you information regarding your account activity and purchases as well as updates about our products and promotional offers. You cannot opt-out of Administrative Emails. “Administrative Emails” relate to a User’s activity on the Website, and include emails regarding a particular User’s account, requests or inquiries, and purchases of products and services. In contrast to Administrative Emails, however, you do have a choice with respect to Promotional Emails. Promotional Emails advertise our products and services, including exclusive sales and other offers, and/or the products and services of our Advertisers and Partners. If you do not want to receive Promotional Emails from us, you may elect to opt-out of receiving Promotional Emails at any time after registering by emailing us at help@shopback.com, or by hitting the “unsubscribe” link at the bottom of any of our emails. When contacting us, please indicate your name and email address, and state that you do not want to receive any Promotional Emails.

**Security of Information**

We take security seriously and take numerous precautions to protect the security of Personally Identifiable Information. You can access your Personally Identifiable Information on our Website through a password and your email address. This password is encrypted. We recommend that you do not share your password with anyone. In addition, your Personally Identifiable Information resides on a secure server that only selected personnel and contractors have access to. We encrypt certain sensitive information (such as credit card information) using Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology to ensure that your Personally Identifiable Information is safe as it is transmitted to us. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we employ commercially reasonable security measures to protect data and seek to partner with companies which do the same, we cannot guarantee the security of any information transmitted to or from the Website, and are not responsible for the actions of any third parties that may receive any such information.

**Data Tracking**

Cookies: To ensure you get cashback successfully when shopping through ShopBack, we store cookies on your computer. A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a User’s computer for record-keeping purposes which contains information about that User. We also use cookies to save you time while using the Website, remind us who you are, and track and target User interests in order to provide a customized experience. Cookies also allow us to collect Non-Personally Identifiable Information from you, like which pages you visited and what links you clicked on. Use of this information helps us to create a more user-friendly experience for all visitors. In addition, we may use Third Party Advertising Companies to display advertisements on our Website. As part of their service, they may place separate cookies on your computer. We have no access to or control over these cookies. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by our Website only and does not cover the use of cookies by any Advertiser. Most browsers automatically accept cookies, but you may be able to modify your browser settings to decline cookies. Please note that if you decline or delete these cookies, you will not be able to receive cashback successfully. Other Tracking Devices: We may use other industry standard technologies like pixel tags and web beacons to track your use of our Website pages and promotions, or we may allow our Third Party Service Providers to use these devices on our behalf. Pixel tags and web beacons are tiny graphic images placed on certain pages on our Website, or in our emails that allow us to determine whether you have performed a specific action. When you access these pages or open or click an email, pixel tags and web beacons generate a Non-Personally Identifiable notice of that action. Pixel tags allow us to measure and improve our understanding of visitor traffic and behavior on our Website, as well as give us a way to measure our promotions and performance. We may also utilize pixel tags and web beacons provided by our Partners for the same purposes.

**Privacy Policies of Third Party Websites**

This Privacy Policy only addresses the use and disclosure of information we collect from you on ShopBack and its related sites. Other Merchant Partner websites that may be accessible through this Website have their own privacy policies and data collection, use and disclosure practices. If you link to any such website, we urge you to review the website’s privacy policy. We are not responsible for the policies or practices of third parties.

**Miscellaneous Privacy Issues**

Public Areas: We may provide areas on our Website where you can publicly post information about yourself, can communicate with others such as discussion boards or blogs, or can review products, restaurants, and submit media content. This information may be accessible by other consumers and companies and may appear on other websites or web searches, and therefore this information could be read, collected, and used by others. We have no control over who reads your postings or what other users may do with the information you voluntarily post, so please use caution when posting any personal information. We do obtain consent from our users to post their name along with their reviews. Facebook: ShopBack allows users to sign up on ShopBack via their Facebook accounts. By proceeding you are allowing ShopBack to access your information and you are agreeing to the Facebook Terms of Use in your use of ShopBack and its related sites.

**Personal Data Notice**

In compliance with the Act, please visit our Personal Data Notice [here](http://www.shopback.com/help/privacysecurity#pdpamypdn).

* * *

### Personal Data Notice – Malaysia

ShopBack Malaysia

\- Personal Data Notice -

In compliance with the Personal Data Protection Act 2010 _ _ and its regulations _,  _this notice is issued to all our valued customers and/ or prospective customers. This Notice will inform you of your rights with regards to your personal data that has been and/ or will be, collected and processed by us.

1.   Collection and processing of personal data

We have collected and will collect your personal data to be processed by us and/ or on your behalf in the course of your present or future dealings with ShopBack, its  subsidiary(ies), its associated company(ies), its joint venture partners,  including of all of its shareholder(s), its director(s), its employee(s), its supplier(s), its contractor(s) and/ or its permitted person(s) (“we”, “our”, “us” or “Company”). Your personal data enables us to achieve the Purpose in clause 3 herein that are in connection with our business.

 2.   Description of personal data

The personal data that you will provide may include but not limited to your name, age, identity card number or passport number, address of correspondence, including office address, gender, date of birth, marital status, details of children and/or guardian(s), occupation, income range, contact information, including e-mail address, mobile number, house number, facsimile number, and office number, details of employer, details of dependants and/or family members, lifestyle preferences, race, religion, nationality.

 3.   Purpose

The collection and processing of personal data includes but not limited to the following purposes:

1\. Agreements & Arrangements

  * Entry into necessary agreements, contracts, memorandum, and/or arrangements to purchase the products or services from us, including sale and purchase agreement, deed of mutual covenant, etc;
  * Credit assessments and other background checks as deemed necessary or appropriate by us;
  * Collection of outstanding payments from our clients under the agreements;
  * Delivery of notice, documents, forms, and other documents under the agreements, contracts, memorandum and/or arrangements;
  * Necessary performance of other obligations under the agreements, contracts, memorandum and/or arrangements;

2\. Services & Products

  * Delivery of our main services and products or products whether present or future;
  * Customer relationship management procedures whichever we deem necessary and fit;
  * Client profiling activities in connection with our services and products;
  * Communication with you and delivery of information by e-mail, telecommunication means, including telephone calls or text messages or social media about products and services offered by Class Of Third Parties under clause 8 herein;
  * Such other purposes provided for in our particular services or products offered by us;

3\. Internal Record & External (Marketing)

  * Marketing of our products/ services to you whether present or future;
  * For purposes relating to any of the above, including but not limited to research, benchmarking and statistical analysis;
  * Internal record keeping;

4\. Legal Compliance

  * Prevention, hindrance, reporting of any crime including but not limited to fraud, bribery and money laundering;
  * Compliance to any legal or regulatory requirements relating to the provision of our services/ products and to make disclosure under the requirements of any applicable law, regulation, direction, court order, order, by-law, guideline, circular, code applicable to us or any associated, subsidiary, related companies of our group. ** **

**4.    Sources**

The sources that we may obtain your personal data includes but not limited to booking forms, registration forms, online forms, agreements you have signed, name cards or any identity materials that you have distributed voluntarily; and business directory(ies) or listing(s) that you have subscribed to share your information, etc.

5.   Class of Third Parties

Generally, your personal data with us will be kept confidential. You hereby consent and authorize us to disclose your personal data to the following categories of third parties:

  1. our associated, subsidiary, related companies of the Company;
  2. our business partners including online business affiliates, retailers, distributors, agents, merchant that provide, supply, distribute or deal in general with our services or products in connection with our business and in relation to our loyalty programs and  _other programs;_
  3. our auditors, engineers, quantity surveyors, land surveyors, business consultants, accountants, lawyers or other professional advisers and/or consultants as we deem necessary and appropriate;
  4. our sub-contractors or third party service or product providers as we deem necessary or appropriate, including third party property management or marketing companies or entities;
  5. any person to whom we are compelled to or required under law or in response to a local or state or federal authority, industry regulator, enforcement agency, statutory authority, court of laws, tribunal, arbitration centre, commission or council  or  association legally authorized by law.

6.   Your Obligations

It is obligatory for you to supply your personal data to us in the most accurate manner. Failing which, we are unable to process your personal data on your behalf and for the Purpose stated in clause 3 herein and all relationships created or to be created between us shall then be terminated and ceased to be in effect immediately.

7.   Your Rights

1\. Right to request access to personal data: You are entitled to request access to your personal data that is processed by us with reasonable notice.

2\. Right to request correction of personal data: You are entitled to request the correction of your personal data that is held by us with reasonable notice. With respect to this, you may: i.       request correction and/ or update of your personal data that is inaccurate, incomplete or out-of-date;  and ii.       request retention of your personal data only as long as necessary for the fulfillment of the Purpose stated in clause 3 herein.

3\. Rights to limit processing of your personal data: You are entitled to limit our processing of your personal data by expressly withdrawing in full, your consent given previously, in each case, including for direct marketing purposes subject to any applicable legal restrictions, contractual conditions and within a reasonable time period.

8.   Contact to make inquiries and complaints regarding personal data 

If you intend to exercise your rights in clause 7 or to make inquiries or complaints regarding your personal data, our policies, procedures in relation to processing your personal data, you may contact the relevant department as follows:

  * Department: ShopBack Customer Team
  * Contact No.: (+60) 1548 48 0011
  * E-mail address: help[@s](mailto:customer@zalora.com.my)hopback.com

9.   Other information

You may visit our website [here](http://www.shopback.com/help/privacysecurity#pdpamy) to learn more about our privacy policy.

* * *

### Citibank Terms and Conditions (Singapore)

Citibank Cards – Online Cashback Promotion **Terms and Conditions**

  1. “Promotion” refers to the “Citibank Cards- Online Cashback Promotion” which is a Promotion organized by Ecommerce Enablers Pte Ltd
  2. Citibank Credit Cardmembers (“Cardmembers”) who choose to participate in the  Promotion will be subject to the Promotion terms and conditions available at [www.shopback.sg](https://www.shopback.sg/)
  3. The qualifying period for the Promotion is from 1 Jan 2015 to 31 Jul 2015 both days inclusive (“Qualifying Period”).
  4. All enquiries or disputes regarding the Promotion shall be referred to Ecommerce Enablers Pte Ltd
  5. Cardmembers may participate in the Promotion by going to [www.shopback.sg/citibank](http://www.shopback.sg/citibank)[ ](https://www.shopback.sg/citibank)and signing up using their first 8 digits of their Citibank Credit Card number.
  6. Cardmembers may only signup in this Promotion once. Partner reserves the right to cancel fraudulent accounts.
  7. The Promotion entitles Cardmembers to cashback at listed merchants which Cardmembers can enjoy only if they make payment using their Citibank Credit Card.
  8. To be entitled to cashback, Cardmembers have to access the participating merchants’ websites by clicking through from <https://www.shopback.sg/citibank>. Cardmembers who access the participating merchants’ websites directly will not receive cashback.
  9. Cardmembers are to make the purchase on the same device that they click through on.
  10. Cardmembers have to enable their cookies to allow their cashback to be tracked
  11. Should any order not be tracked, Cardmembers are to reach out to ShopBack at [citi.help@shopback.sg](mailto:citi.help@shopback.sg).
  12. Individual merchant terms and conditions apply
  13. Card Members consent to providing their email or account details to ShopBack for refund of the cashback. This process is solely managed by ShopBack and all related enquiries or disputes should be sent to [citi.help@shopback.sg](mailto:citi.help@shopback.sg).
  14. Citibank is not the organizer of the Promotion and is also not the supplier of any products/services purchased in connection with the Promotion  and will not accept any liability in relation thereto. Citibank does not endorse and shall not be responsible for the quality, merchantability or the fitness for any purpose or any other aspect of the products and/or services provided by third parties. Citibank shall not at any time be responsible or held liable for any loss, injury, damage or harm suffered by or in connection with the products and/or services provided by third parties.
  15. “Citibank” means Citibank Singapore Limited

* * *

### Citibank Globeshopper Terms & Conditions (Singapore)

**Please  note that only purchases made from the following merchants are eligible for the $10 Bonus Cashback:**

**9**  

**A**  

**B**  

**C**  

**D**  

**E**  

**F**  

**G**  

**H**  

**J**  

**K**  

**L**  

**M**  

**N**  

**O**  

**P**  

**Q**  

**R**  

**S**  

**T**  

**V**  

**Y**  

Additional Terms & Conditions

  1. S$10 Bonus Cashback will only be awarded with S$100 minimum spend on overseas merchants* (travel sites not included)
  2. S$10 Bonus Cashback will be credited on 1st July
  3. Customers must have a valid ShopBack account to enjoy this promotion
  4. Users are required to click through ShopBack’s “Get Cashback” button and complete purchase within the same window to qualify for Cashback
  5. Cashback will only be awarded for legitimate completed transactions. Cancellations, returns or refunds will not be eligible for Cashback
  6. Cashback is not applicable to purchases of gift cards, taxes, delivery charges, as well as purchases made on merchant’s mobile apps
  7. Please note that use of any voucher codes not provided on ShopBack’s website may affect your eligibility for cashback
  8. This campaign is only valid for Citibank cardholders
  9. All enquires and disputes regarding this promotion shall be referred to ShopBack.
  10. Citibank users are still eligible for S$10 sign up bonus on Citi Rewards Card and S$5 sign up bonus for all other Citibank Cards
